Tay：我哋會接住你
【啦啦隊隊長 TAY TAWAN】
【準備好接住佢喇！！】
【噢！！】
佢頭幾步行得幾好，之後就就嚟跌噉
【佢嚇到個心離一離】
【繼續行唔好停啊】
【抖下先】
佢係到做咩啊？
佢會繼續行定放棄呢？
仲計緊時㗎佢要快啲決定好
【MIX 加油啊！！】
【見到都凳佢覺得驚】
希望 First 望完佢個 friend 玩唔會覺得驚
【佢一直望住 Mix】
加油啊勇敢啲
：Mix，繼續行
放鬆啲
【佢有一顆堅決嘅心】
【搖下搖下噉】
Tay：舊金等緊你
【佢講嘅嘢好無理頭】
Tay：Mix，加油
Tay：White，去同佢打下氣啦
【離終點唔遠喇】
【佢尖叫等自己冇咁驚】
Tay：嗌出嚟啦
【用你嘅 energy 啦】
Team C 偷偷地練習緊要點行
【就到喇】
【最後 3 個氣球】
Team B：喺你上面
【得咗喇】
Nicky：Mix，你好勁
First：估唔到
Nicky：好勁
Tay：好快
Mix：我對腳仲震緊
Gun：佢對腳震緊因為佢怕高
【佢對腳好唔合作】
Leo：我哋大鑊喇
Nicky：唔緊要，First，冇事嘅
Leo：唔好望地下
【試緊安慰佢】
Mix：好得人驚，好高
啲板會搖
我要平衡到先
一個唔小心就會跌咗落嚟
【佢仲好攰】
Mix：我對腳震緊
我好驚
我行得好快因為 P’ Boy 話如果我贏咗會額外有錢
【佢為咗奬金好努力】
Tay：佢最勁係佢嗌出嚟等自己冇咁驚
佢由第一下到最後一下都嗌得好好
如果佢跌咗落嚟我哋會跑開
佢跌落地之後我會跑番嚟幫佢
White：你係一個壞朋友
Mix：我相信我贏到 First
【睇下點】
First：我想像同現實
Nanon：恐怖啲？
First：恐怖過我諗
Nanon：唔緊要呢兩個哥哥會精神上支持你
Mix：唔緊要㗎 First 我嘅朋友
我都過咗
White：小心唔好跌落嚟
Leo：放鬆啲 First 冇嘢高得過我哋個心
Mix：我示範咗點做喇，到你做一次
First：我嬲喇
睇住嚟
Mix：我會等住睇你
【冷靜啲兄弟】
First：睇住嚟啦
未睇到你點玩但口講就第一
Team A：放鬆
Nanon：一步一步嚟
【慢但好安全】
Nanon：繼續行
：左，右
Team A：幾快喎
【佢好興奮】
Team A：繼續行
【堆人好激動】
Mix：First 小心
First 嘗試小心啲等自己冇咁驚
佢啲隊員仲激動過佢
Team A：First 你做得好好啊
【佢哋好大聲】
【研究緊對手】
Team C 好靜噉觀察緊
Team C 好靜噉觀察緊佢
佢哋好驚定計劃緊啲咩？
Team A：放鬆啲
【就到喇】
【佢wu低個人】
Arm：佢用咗呢個技巧
HERE COMES THE DOUBLE-KNEE STRIKE.
【加油啊兄弟】
Mix：佢幾快
【佢加速緊】
【佢開始搖】
Mix：佢同我邊個快啲？
【佢用唇語表達咗出嚟】
Mix：我同 First 邊個快啲
Tay：差唔多
【佢改咗佢嘅反應】
【就完喇】
【差一步咋】
Mix：佢唔似我，佢冇嘥時間喺拮個波度
Team A：就到喇
【佢聲援緊 First】
最後一個波喇，First，快啲完咗佢
【做得好】
First：都唔係咁得人驚啫
Nicky：幾快喎
First：冇我想像中咁得人驚
【依家佢口講好勁】
First：點解你要咁耐？
Mix：我拮唔中啲波
Mond：First，你好快
Off：我中意你呢個技巧
【我中意】
Sing：真係好快
Chimon：唔緊要，我哋仲有 Sing
The soldier doesn’t end, don’t count the war.
The war hasn’t ended.
First：都唔係咁得人驚
我快唔快？我覺得我幾快
【佢依家好 high】
呢嗰係我隱藏嘅能力嚟
我覺得我玩遊戲發掘到潛能幾好
Staff：可唔可以講下你真實嘅感受
First：我對腳由行第一步開始震緊
Staff：點解你冇嗌出嚟？
First：我驚到嗌唔出
玩緊嗰陣覺得好驚
不過爬落嚟嗰陣仲驚
Leo：First 觀察得 Mix 好好
Mix 好慢同好耐先完成
以我嘅觀察 First 快啲
Gun：佢可能快過我𠻹
Nicky：原本我以為你會慢過 Mix
但你開始嗰陣，你有你嘅節奏同冇乜點錯
【嚟讚下佢】
到最後一隊玩喇
睇咗咁耐，Earth，你係時候 show 下實力畀人睇
Off：你睇咗前 2 個人玩未？
Earth：睇咗
Off：佢哋你業餘嘅
但你係...
Earth：...一束
Earth：我可以話我係第一嘅
【好有自信】
Tay：聽住喇，有人想同你講啲嘢
Mix：你得㗎
【精神上嘅鼓勵】
Earth：多謝
He didn’t know it was our plan.
But he gains strength from it.
Then our plan went wrong.
Will Tay’s plan to falsely praise Earth work?
Let’s see.
Go. Keep going.
The game is over.
SUPER FAST.
ARE YOU IN A RUSH?
Tay’s plan doesn’t work with Earth.
He is unstoppable and as fast as lightning.
HE DOESN’T MAKE A SINGLE MISTAKE.
SUPER SCARY.
He’s very fast.
HE’S THE REAL DEAL.
Take it easy, Earth.
WHY IS HE SO FAST?
WHAT WAS YOUR PLAN?
THE PLAN FAILS.
HE IS SO CHILL.
Earth is going forwards at a fast speed.
He’s not afraid nor stoppable.
He’s too strong.
THEY FEEL RELAXED NOW.
Pierce it. Left and right.
HE’S NOT SLOWING DOWN AT ALL.
EARTH IS COMING.
AMAZING.
GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
SO PROUD.
Your plan to cheer for him.
The plan went wrong.
Let’s get him some support so he would be overconfident.
But he did so well.
THANK YOU, BUDDY.
Did you see it?
It’s like we already won since the first round.
I’m not here to lose. I’m here to win.
I’M SERIOUS.
You kept stepping forward nonstop.
Yes, but deep down, I was nervous.
But I only thought I had to do it faster than the other two teams.
Were your scared/
I’m not afraid of height.
First was wrong. This time I won’t take it easy on him.
I’M HERE TO WIN.
Let’s give Earth round applause.
First was wrong. This time I won’t take it easy on him.
THE PRIDE OF THE TEAM.
Let’s give Earth round applause.
How was I?
You were very fast. I thought you were the god of thunder.
He made me unexpectedly proud.
I thought he would be hasty.
But he wasn’t at all.
There is a jealous team next to us.
DON’T SHOW IT.
Where?
This is easy.
The next round will be easy too.
Yes, if Sing starts the game.
But I’m worried about Gun.
Gun will be fast.
Don’t say you are worried. Say you are afraid.
IS IT THAT BAD?
When it comes to speed, he is no.1.
This fun in this week is over.
But don’t be so quick to judge.
It’s not certain who will win the game.
The first round allows the three new
rangers – First, Earth, and Mix to show their potential.
They all have fighting spirits.
They will be able to compete with the veteran rangers just fine.
How will the result of this game turn out? Check it out next week.
Thank you, the Verona at Tab Lan in Prachinburi, for the filming location.
It’s close to Bangkok, with only 2-3 hours of driving.
The air is fresh and the accommodations are comfortable.
It’s a great place for a family vacation.
If you are an adventure lover, there are many obstacles for you to enjoy.
There’s also a flower garden for photo shooting.
Thank you.
The players in the second round are also as good as those in the first round.
Who will win the first game?
Find out in the next episode, airing next Saturday at noon.